{
  "2017-06-01": [
    {
      "name": "insomnia",
      "type": "rating",
      "problem": true,
      "question": "Did you experience insomnia?",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "wake-up",
      "type": "time",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "When did you wake up?",
      "answer": "6.75"
    },
    {
      "name": "go-to-bed",
      "type": "time",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "When did you go to bed?",
      "answer": "22.75"
    },
    {
      "name": "naps",
      "type": "rating",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "Did you take any naps?",
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "name": "caffeine",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many units of caffeine did you have (a unit is 8 oz of coffee or tea, 20 oz of caffeinated soda)?",
      "answer": 6
    },
    {
      "name": "alcohol",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many units of alcohol did you have (a unit is 12 oz of beer, 5 oz of wine, 1.5 oz of liquor)?",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "name": "exercise-strength",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many minutes of strength training did you do, such as lifting weights or doing push ups?",
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "name": "exercise-aerobic",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many minutes of aerobic exercise did you do, such as jogging or cycling?",
      "answer": 40
    },
    {
      "name": "walking",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many minutes of walking did you do?",
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "name": "work",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many hours of work did you do, including professional and personal work?",
      "answer": 4
    }
  ],
  "2017-06-02": [
    {
      "name": "insomnia",
      "type": "rating",
      "problem": true,
      "question": "Did you experience insomnia?",
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "name": "wake-up",
      "type": "time",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "When did you wake up?",
      "answer": "6.5"
    },
    {
      "name": "go-to-bed",
      "type": "time",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "When did you go to bed?",
      "answer": "22.75"
    },
    {
      "name": "naps",
      "type": "rating",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "Did you take any naps?",
      "answer": 25
    },
    {
      "name": "caffeine",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many units of caffeine did you have (a unit is 8 oz of coffee or tea, 20 oz of caffeinated soda)?",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "alcohol",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many units of alcohol did you have (a unit is 12 oz of beer, 5 oz of wine, 1.5 oz of liquor)?",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "exercise-strength",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many minutes of strength training did you do, such as lifting weights or doing push ups?",
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "name": "exercise-aerobic",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many minutes of aerobic exercise did you do, such as jogging or cycling?",
      "answer": 25
    },
    {
      "name": "walking",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many minutes of walking did you do?",
      "answer": 30
    },
    {
      "name": "work",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many hours of work did you do, including professional and personal work?",
      "answer": 2
    }
  ],
  "2017-06-03": [
    {
      "name": "insomnia",
      "type": "rating",
      "problem": true,
      "question": "Did you experience insomnia?",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "wake-up",
      "type": "time",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "When did you wake up?",
      "answer": "6.75"
    },
    {
      "name": "go-to-bed",
      "type": "time",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "When did you go to bed?",
      "answer": 23
    },
    {
      "name": "naps",
      "type": "rating",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "Did you take any naps?",
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "name": "caffeine",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many units of caffeine did you have (a unit is 8 oz of coffee or tea, 20 oz of caffeinated soda)?",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "name": "alcohol",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many units of alcohol did you have (a unit is 12 oz of beer, 5 oz of wine, 1.5 oz of liquor)?",
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "name": "exercise-strength",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many minutes of strength training did you do, such as lifting weights or doing push ups?",
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "name": "exercise-aerobic",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many minutes of aerobic exercise did you do, such as jogging or cycling?",
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "name": "walking",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many minutes of walking did you do?",
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "name": "work",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many hours of work did you do, including professional and personal work?",
      "answer": 8
    }
  ],
  "2017-06-04": [
    {
      "name": "insomnia",
      "type": "rating",
      "problem": true,
      "question": "Did you experience insomnia?",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "name": "wake-up",
      "type": "time",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "When did you wake up?",
      "answer": "6.25"
    },
    {
      "name": "go-to-bed",
      "type": "time",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "When did you go to bed?",
      "answer": "22.75"
    },
    {
      "name": "naps",
      "type": "rating",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "Did you take any naps?",
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "name": "caffeine",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many units of caffeine did you have (a unit is 8 oz of coffee or tea, 20 oz of caffeinated soda)?",
      "answer": 5
    },
    {
      "name": "alcohol",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many units of alcohol did you have (a unit is 12 oz of beer, 5 oz of wine, 1.5 oz of liquor)?",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "name": "exercise-strength",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many minutes of strength training did you do, such as lifting weights or doing push ups?",
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "name": "exercise-aerobic",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many minutes of aerobic exercise did you do, such as jogging or cycling?",
      "answer": 40
    },
    {
      "name": "walking",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many minutes of walking did you do?",
      "answer": 20
    },
    {
      "name": "work",
      "type": "amount",
      "problem": false,
      "question": "How many hours of work did you do, including professional and personal work?",
      "answer": 8
    }
  ]
}
